[ Watch on kissFlix.co ]
What the hell are you doing?
From that angle, my double chin
must be showing.
MY SOON-TO-BE BF IS SO TALENTED
Bay! you didn’t post that on Close Friends!
If my dad finds out,
I’ll just come out to him.
Chun, do you know about this?!
Sun!
Focus!
You two can do this!
You better win this!
I’ll show you, Dad.
Good luck, Sun.
Thank you.
Here.
Thank you so much.
(Good luck, Sun.)
I’m kind of sad.
-(May I put this on you?)
-(Oh, sure.)
Bay, are you sad you’ll be far away
from your boo?
-Nope.
-(Here.)
(Thank you so much.)
-Can I write something on your shirt?
-Of course.
I won’t let anything keep us apart.
Ooh.
“I won’t let anything keep us apart.”
That is so sweet, bro.
Oh, shut up.
Thank you, guys.
SUPPORTED BY THE DEPARTMENT OF CULTURAL PROMOTION,
MINISTRY OF CULTURE
AT BANGKOK PIPAT SCHOOL
Ally, pass me the mic.
Too bad Sun can’t be with us untill
the end of this semester.
I’ll find the time to visit and play with you guys.
Then will you be able to come to prom?
I think the principal will allow it.
But I don’t know if I’ll be available then.
If you can, you have to come, okay?
Ally and I have made a plan.
-Don’t worry about that now!
-Let’s just sing.
Don’t worry about it. Cheers.
Cheers!!
-Cheers!
-Cheers! Yay!
Come on, girls.
Petong, sing.
Petong, come on.
Are you sad?
Mmm.
I kind of am.
I don’t know if…when I’m at the camp,
I can still live a normal life like this.
Hey!
Don’t worry about that.
It might be just as fun there.
Right?
Don’t worry.
Please! This is not your honeymoon.
Come sing with us.
-Come on, come on
-Come on. Let’s sing.
Go, go, go.
SAMING PHON FAI
Why don’t you just join him?
So I don’t have to see your face anymore.
Hey, hey, hey.
If you have such a problem with it,
why don’t you just move?!
Should I call a rescue truck to take you away?
-Are you wishing me dead, Chun?!
-Yes!
-Assh*le!
-Dad!
Dad!
A customer called about the Merit making ceremony.
You should go talk to him. He’s waiting.
-You’re saved by the bell.
-Oh, please.
Or someone’s gonna have to book
a funeral hall for you.
-Damn you!
-Just go.
Oh, I’m so scared.
-Just stop it.
-Go! Get lost!
Damn it.
But honestly,
it’s good you’re moving to the dorm.
What do you mean, Pa?
I’m not comfortable with you hanging out
with that boy.
Why, Pa?
Bay is not a bad guy.
You see?
You just played with him once, and now
you’re defending him.
His dad is so horrible, and the apple
doesn’t fall far from the tree.
It’s best to stay away from him.
SAMING PHON FAI
What are you smiling about?
Nothing, Pa.
I’m just happy you care so much about me.
Of course I do.
You’re the only one I have left.
I care about you too, Pa.
ATHLETES’ DORMITORY
You’ve got everything?
Make sure you don’t forget anything.
Why are there so few items?
These are all, Pa.
Are you sure you can be alone?
I’ll be fine, Pa. I can stay by myself.
If the water stops running, the power goes out,
the AC breaks down, or the pipes get clogged,
just let me know. I’ll come take a look.
Okay.
When I’m free, I’ll go visit you at home
right away.
I’ll leave then.
Goodbye, Pa.
-Take care of yourself.
-Okay.
-You too, Pa.
-Yeah.
Goodbye, Pa.
You forgot something, Pa?
Surprise!
What’s wrong?
My dad just left.
Quiet.
Go over there.
Is that where your mom lives,
across the street?
Mmm.
Why did you follow me here?
Now that your dad’s away,
how could I pass up this opportunity?
-You perv!
-What?
You’re gonna get us caught.
How can we get caught?
I told my dad I would do my portfolio at Petong’s.
I can stay here till 4 a.m. if you want.
You think I have time to play with you?
I’m not here to play.
I’m here to take care of you.
Don’t you have things to do?
Like your portfolio?
That I have to do.
But…I have to do my boyfriend, too.
I can do both at the same time.
Your portfolio?
Sure.
You need a hand?
If you want to give me a hand, you can give me a hand.
NOTIFICATION FIRST DAY OF TRAINING 8 A.M.
How was it?
Everyone was amazing.
-Yeah?
-Mmm.
The process in which a gas accepts an electron
is called Electron Affinity.
This is Step 4, not 3.
I got that.
Hey, hold on.
(Coming home late again.)
(Stay over at Petong’s then.)
Yes!
Let’s continue.
SAMING PHON FAI
Dad.
I’m leaving.
Do you have to stay with your friend for months
to do your portfolio?
Oh, Dad.
I’m going to Italy.
I have to take this seriously.
-Seriously?
-Of course, I’m serious about this.
-See you, Dad.
-Yeah, good luck.
-Yes.
-You’re serious?!
I’m serious, Dad.
Zippo!
Sun!
Long time no see!
-I miss you so much.
-I know. I know.
Okay.
That’s enough. That’s enough.
I know you miss him but come on.
Oh, I miss you too, Bay.
Why would you miss me?
-Miss you.
-Let me go!
-Hey, hey.
-Who said you could hug me?
Sun, Sun, Bay is kicking my butt.
-Guys, play nice.
You miss me, huh?
7.28 seconds. Next
PA: HOW ARE YOU?
I thought those flowers were for me.
I bought them for you.
But can I use them for my drawing first?
I got you something, too.
You did?
Hey! So adorable!
Are these matching bracelets?
Mmm, I’ll put it on you.
Okay.
So?
Very cute.
Let me put yours on.
There you go. Bay and Sun.
So perfect. The school break’s almost over.
These will remind us of each other.
You do love art, don’t you?
Just like how you love tennis.
Mmm.
Does that mean…
you’re really serious
about submitting your portfolio to
a college in Italy?
Mmm, I really am.
But…
Are you okay with us living so far apart?
I’m okay.
Whether you go to Italy or not,
I’ll have to focus on playing for the national
team anyway.
I wouldn’t have that much time for you.
It’s good
that you have something to focus on, too.
Now I don’t have to worry.
How can my boyfriend be so cute?
You cutie.
-Did you steal a kiss on my cheek?
-Yes.
Sun, are you in there?
Sh*t! My dad!
Sh*t! We’re screwed.
A moment, Pa.
I just got out of the shower.
Let me get dressed.
Hi, Pa.
Uhh.
What are you doing here, Pa?
I came to see you. I texted you.
You’ve been leaving me on ‘read’ for days lately.
Forgot about your Pa, huh?
Oh,
how could I forget you, Pa?
I fell asleep right after training all day, Pa.
So, can I help you with something?
Well...
I was just in the neighborhood
so I bought you suki from your favorite shop.
I also wanted to see if you’re doing okay here.
And how are you doing, Pa?
Can I use the bathroom?
-Then I’ll just leave.
-Oh, right that way.
Right there.
Why is he here?
Yes?
I’ll go.
You’re leaving, Pa?
Don’t forget to eat.
Of…
Of course, I’ll eat it, Pa.
You get home safe.
I’ll drop by when I have time.
Get some rest.
You too, Pa.
Take care of yourself.
Goodbye, Pa.
Don’t know why he was here. Sh*t.
He gave me a heart attack.
Thought I’d die before becoming a real artist.
What are you doing here?
Just picking up some stuff.
I’m here to buy some good dinner.
Wanna eat together?
How do you know it’s good?
-Why would I buy it if it wasn’t good.
-Here you go.
Your bill.
Oh, hey.
Boat… You’re Boat, right?
Have you finished your internship at the hospital?
Oh, he’s just… here to visit his family.
Bring another box.
-You must be tired from working too hard.
-Shut up.
-Hey!
Hey, Sorn! Sorn, are you okay?!
Hey, Sorn! Sorn! Sorn!
-Boat! Boat, you’re a doctor! Help!
-Call the police! I mean, call the ambulance!
Boat, he’s dying! Come help him!
Don’t just stand there! Come and help!
Sorn! Sorn!
-What’s wrong with you?
-Boat, help him!
Help! Somebody, help!!
Somebody, help!!
(Hey, stop it.)
Pa!!
How long have you been lying to me, Sun?
Pa, I can explain
Boat,
why didn’t you wear a facemask when you
went out?
They all know about me.
Come inside.
Come talk inside!
We don’t need to talk!
Maybe they already knew about me.
Why, Dad?
Are you embarrassed
to have me as a son?
Why can’t you just be like your brother, huh?
He’s not studying medicine
but he’s brought home
so many rewards, unlike you.
Fine, Dad.
From now on,
I’m not one of your sons anymore.
What the hell?
Boat!
Boat!!
I don’t know
how things will turn out if we talk  to my dad directly.
We’ll get through this.
I will never leave you.
‘Cause you’re my boyfriend.
Now...
What are you gonna do?
I have no idea.
I just don’t wanna go home.
Maybe…
I will stay with my mom at my grandma’s house.
My mom’s there taking care of her.
Then…I’ll figure something out.
If you need anything at all,
let me know, okay?
You can lean on me, always.
Please remember I’m here for you.
Pa…
I...
Bay and I… We’ve been seeing each other
for a while.
I’m sorry, Pa.
Sun…
I’m begging you.
You know what that family has done to us.
They’re the reason your mom and your brother moved out.
Now you’re gonna leave me too?
Dad…
I have something to confess.
Confess? What is it?
Well, now Sun and I,
we are boyfriends, Dad.
You mean Chun’s son?!
Are you insane?
How could you date someone like that?
Why, Dad? Sun doesn’t have anything
to do with your feud.
Of course, he does! You are my son.
How could you ever date Chun’s son?
How would that make me look, huh?!
All you care about is how people see you?
Watch it.
I am your dad.
You don’t get to talk back to me.
Just listen and do as I tell you to do.
-Dad, why can’t you listen to me?
-I’ve been working my ass off raising two sons.
How can both of you be so ungrateful, huh?!
But how is this my fault, Dad?
Fine, it’s not your fault!
But without me, could you have had
all of this, Bay?!
Do you know what I had to do to raise you
so you could grow up
with more opportunities than other people
and never have to owe anyone anything?!
But I’ve never done anything in my life to disappoint you.
-Can’t you just let me be with Sun?
-I can’t!
And if you don’t listen to me,
you are not my son.
Just get out of here. Get out of my sight!!
These damn kids.
Sun!
Why, Sun?!
Are you really giving up this easy?
Even though you’ve given up,
I’ll keep fighting
CALLING BOAT
INCOMING CALL - BAY
Bay.
What’s going on with you?
You came to my house just to sit there?
You’ve been quiet for like an hour.
You should tell your big brother at least.
BOAT (3)
Who’s been calling?
No one, Mom.
Just some scammer.
Did you come here because there’s something
going on at home?
No, Mom.
I just wanted to see Grandma.
Hmm.
I’m getting tired. I’ll go take a shower.
Be with Grandma, okay?
Sun’s mom!
-Keep it down, boy!
-Sun’s mom!
You can’t be yelling here, boy.
Why not?
-Come with me.
-Hey, what are you doing?
-Come on.
-I’m not going with you?
Bay, is that you?
Sun’s mom, hello.
I’ll get to the training, Dad.
I’ll pick you up in the evening.
Okay.
Sun!
Your dad has left.
I understand
that your dad has to come first.
I’m not mad.
But I’m not giving up on us that easily.
In my eyes,
you’re still my boyfriend
And I know you don’t want us to break up, either.
But I can’t choose you.
What about our promise, Sun?
You and me.
An artist and a national athlete.
You go be an artist.
And I’ll be a national athlete.
But we won’t be boyfriends.
Can’t you read the sign?
‘FAMILY MEMBERS ONLY’
You have never changed.
What are you doing here?
Bay came to see me.
You don’t have the rights to dictate
what those boys do.
Our marriage was ruined because of you.
-It was because of Bee.
-Chun.
Whether Bee stole your family’s recipe or not,
you don’t have to hold a grudge
for the rest of your life.
And there’s no need to drag me and your children
into your feud.
-It’s him...
-Chun
I didn’t leave you because of someone else.
It’s because you still can’t let this go.
I should’ve taken Sun with me too.
Then you could’ve fought with Bee
without causing Sun all this pain.
If you want to hold a grudge,
then do it on your own.
If you cared about your son
and saw what truly makes him happy,
you wouldn’t be acting like this.
Hey, hang on.
Can you come with me?
To where?
Just trust me.
Bay.
If this doesn’t work,
you won’t have to see me again.
(Going back to my old school for a bit.
I’ll go straight home when I’m done.)
-Why did you take me here?
-Come on, quick.
You ready?
Ready for what?
I don’t even know why I’m here.
You don’t have to know.
Just do whatever you want to do.
Okay?
Let’s go.
Come on.
What is all this?
It’s our prom.
I didn’t want you to miss out on anything more.
Isn’t this all we wanted, Sun?
Just to live a normal life, like a normal kid.
Make our own decisions.
Do you think that’s impossible, Sun?
I’m so sorry.
-I should have kept fighting for us.
-It’s okay.
It’s all right.
I understand.
And I’m not mad at you at all.
Please be my genuine, simple Sun again.
I’m really sorry.
It’s okay.
I know how you feel, really.
♪ Ever since that day ♪
♪ When you and I happened to meet, it’s like a dream ♪
♪ ’Cause you’re the one ♪
♪ Who came along and made my heart skip a beat ♪
♪ It feels like I’ve finally found love ♪
Pa!
I’m the one who took Sun here.
I’m sorry I didn’t ask you first.
And I’m sorry
that I didn’t tell you
that I was dating Sun.
But I really love him.
I know
you really hate my dad.
But can you please not hate me?
Pa.
I’m begging you.
Can you let me live like a normal kid for a night?
Just don’t come home too late.
Make sure you take him home by 11.
You hear me?
Yes, sir.
Thank you for fighting for me.
Thank you, too, for coming with me.
Hey! What was that?!
Do that again.
I wasn’t ready for that.
Please.
Please pretty please.
- Please pretty please.
-No, that’s enough.
That’s enough.
Why?
We’ve got your dad’s approval.
♪ You’re the only one I’ll ever give a Like ♪
♪ Want, want you to come and be
a part of my life ♪
♪ Morning, afternoon, or all night,
I’ll always make you smile ♪
♪ No matter how many seconds pass,
I promise I’ll never make you cry ♪
♪ I’ll hold you tight ♪
♪ Never let you out of my sight ♪
♪ Stay by my side ♪
♪ We don’t need the stars to tell us this is real ♪
♪ We don’t have to wait for some day
they say is special ♪
♪ I’m giving you my whole heart ♪
Where are you staying tonight, Bay?
I can stay at my friend’s place, sir.
It’s late. You can sleep with Sun tonight.
If you walk away, don’t ever come back again, you brat!
Unless you stop seeing that boy.
You don’t have to carry this on
your shoulders, Bay.
I’m here for you, always.